

Kirill Elizarov .NET Developer

- Prague, Czech Republic
- **&** +420779970567
- @ kiril.elizarov@gmail.com

Links

in Kirill Elizarov



Skills

Technical Skills

a.k.a. buzzwords

C#, REST API, NUnit, Entity Framework, Angular, React, ASP webforms, Azure, PostgreSQL, Oracle, MS SQL, TFS, git, TeamCity, Rider, VS, ReSharper, Postman, .Net Core, Vue.js, Episerver, Docker, k8s, Python, LLM, Octopus

Languages

Czech

Advanced professional proficiency

English

Upper intermediate



Russian

Native proficiency



Systems Design Fundamentals AlgoExpert

Comprehensive systems design

fundamentals certification

Angular 2 Basic angular.cz

February 2019

Comprehensive training in Angular 2 framework and development practices

React JS and Redux Bootcamp udemy 2019

Comprehensive React and Redux development course

Interests

Hobbies

Game development (Unity), IoT, squash, hiking, tennis

Software engineer with 10 years of experience in developing complex applications in the banking, e-commerce and B2B sectors. Experienced in leading teams and developing new products from scratch within strict deadlines and providing long-term support for systems with large backlogs. Strong focus on architectural solutions and technical leadership.

Experience

First Line Software

April 2021 - Present Prague, CZ

Senior .NET Developer & Tech Lead https://firstlinesoftware.com/

Kin+Carta various projects, development:

- Successfully participated in development and delivey over 10 enterprise-level projects, including implementations for major clients such as Pizza Hut and the UK National Football League
- Enhanced Episerver CMS platform with advanced features including AIpowered content recommendations and search result optimization

Triptych, technical leadership:

- Led the development of the Triptych sales content management platform, with particular focus on scalability, security, and seamless CRM integration
- Architected and implemented core platform features, including sophisticated content customization tools and advanced analytics capabilities
- Orchestrated client communications and feature rollouts, ensuring alignment with business objectives and stakeholder requirements
- Spearheaded the migration to microservices architecture while modernizing infrastructure to implement robust CI/CD practices and enhance system resilience

SKB Kontur

March 2020 - December 2020

Prague CZ

Back End Developer, Team Leader

- Led the development of a service for small businesses: an Electronic Sales Registration (ESR) system
- Key responsibilities:
 - System design and task delegation
 - API development
 - Maintenance of technical documentation
 - CI/CD configuring

Cleverlance

August 2017 - March 2021

Prague, CZ

.NET Developer

https://www.cleverlance.com

- Development of an application for approving corporate credit products, covering the entire approval workflow: tasks, design and approval of financing, risk analysis, contractual documentation, and loan drawdown
- Key responsibilities:
 - Design and implementation of architectural solutions based on functional specifications
 - Incident management

Spring Systems, s.r.o. ASP.NET Developer

October 2015 - July 2017 Prague CZ

- Development and support of a benefit system
- Key contributions:
 - Development of a tree-like task management system with change history tracking
 - Creating demo versions and prototyping new features

Education

Ural State University Applied Mathematics

September 2007 - August 2012

Full-time

Bachelor's degree in Applied Mathematics with focus on software development and mathematical modeling